Hello everyone, Welcome to the Milanam presentation. At Milanam,
we are building an experience layer on top of NFTs.
So, we are building token gated video rooms and audio rooms
where people can enter if they have a proof ownership
of a particular NFT. They enter that room and they can experience something together
they can create something together with that exclusive community.
So,
how it works is that you know people can join or these video rooms they can
do lots of stuff. They have like plugins to play games, stream videos
work on white boards together you know the usual chatting audio, video we have those things you know
to addon to it. So, let's get into it like how it works
the user connect their phantom wallet
once the wallet is connected oh you know we can go over to
the dashboard which shows all the NFTs I own
and what sort of rooms I can create.
So, these are my NFT collections and I can create a room out of
these
and that room will have this exclusive property that only people who
own this NFT can join. So, if I want to create like a
the T-Shirt room
so, I can go here and you know i can set
the room title, room description and other stuff. So, lets
add it here... I can do and create this meeting
then i can also join other live meetings which are happening on the platform
if they're happening...
and these are some of the previous meetings that I'd created. So, if I view these details
I can
joined this meetup
once i gave the appropriate permissions i get to join the room
and he we go so this is the video space where the interactions really
happens and then there is these plugins which I can add. We have you know remote browser
,watching youtube videos and drawing, playing games and collaborating
over white board or trello
so we have all these of plugins to go with it. So, this is like an exclusive space
which only the T-shirt NFT holders can only join.
So, this is the genesis product that we have
But ...
the idea came to us when we are saving our own problem we have been building the floorgang
community which is like a community of NFT collectors and investors for some time and
we saw this problem when we interacted with dozens of NFT creators
who were running the communities
so that's how the idea of Milanam came about. And we are very excited
to paticipate in this hackathon and get get some solid feedback to build
the next big experience here layer on top of NFTs.
Thank You